const questions = [
    {
    id: 1,
    Question: 'Am I speaking with <YOUR NAME>?',
    Answer:
      'Yes,this is <YOUR NAME> speaking',
    },
  
    {
      id: 2,
      Question: 'Are you looking for a job change?',
      Answer:
        'Yes, I am looking for a job change',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      Question: 'Ok, may i know your experience?',
      Answer:
        'Sure,I have overall 3 years of experience in Html,CSS,boostrap and i have 2 years of experience in javascript and React',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      Question: 'What is your relevant experience?',
      Answer:
        'If i talk about my Reactjs experience, Inhave overall 2 years of experience ',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      Question: 'what is your current organisation?',
      Answer:
        'I am currently working with Trangla which service based company,located in Guntur,Andhra Pradesh ',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      Question: 'Can i know about the project that your working on?',
      Answer:
        'Sure,I am working on playat web application.Basically playat is a local playground booking app and some other internal projects',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        Question: 'Tell me something about your Project?',
        Answer:
          'We are currently working on playat application, which a ground booking app nearby hyderabad. It provide user to book slot or ground, like cricket, badminton, football etc.It gives an option to book slot at particular time or It may be full day In these project we are total 8 members, 2 Testers, 3 frontend and 3 backend developers.',
        },
      {
        id: 8,
        Question: 'What is your role in project?',
        Answer:
          'My role in this project was mainly frontend development using technologies reactjs, JavaScript,  html and css. I mainly develop reusable components, dashboard layouts,ui development. This project stack is -Backend: Php laravel, database MySql Frontend: Reactjs, JavaScript,  html and css',
        },
        {
          id: 9,
          Question: 'How many employees in your company',
          Answer:
            'Overall employees in company is 14members. 1 HR, 2 Managers, 3 Testers, 4 backend developers, 4 frontend developers.'
          },
          {
            id: 10,
            Question: 'What is the notice period?',
            Answer:
              'It is one month notice period.But it can negotiable to 15 days',
            },
            {
              id: 11,
              Question: 'How it is negotiable for 15 days?',
              Answer:
                'See,offcially it is one month notice period.But i can able talk with my manager and ask for early relieve',
              },
              {
                id: 12,
                Question: 'Are you immediate joiner?',
                Answer:
                  'No,offcially my notice period is one month.But I can able talk with my manager and ask for early relieve.But at least it will take around 15 days to get relieve',
                },
                {
                  id: 13,
                  Question: 'What is your current CTC?',
                  Answer:
                    'My current CTC is 3.5LPA',
                  },
                  {
                    id: 14,
                    Question: 'What is your expected CTC?',
                    Answer:
                      'I am expecting 6LPA',
                    },
                    {
                      id: 15,
                      Question: 'Is CTC negotiable?',
                      Answer:
                        'Yes, I am open to negotiations',
                      },
                      
  ]
  export default questions